Adrian Hernández Velozo

Spain, M 28019 641-602-126 - ahvelozo@gmail.com

http://www.ahvelozo.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutionsoriented problem-solving. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

WORK HISTORY

11/2018 to 08/2019

Software Engineer

Bios Software S.A – Panamá, Panamá, Ciudad del Saber

 Worked closely with software development and testing team members to design and develop robust e-commerce solutions to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability and performance

09/2016 to 10/2018

Software Engineer and System Administrator

Proyecto Espacios – Cuba, La Havana

- Design, develop, deploy & maintain the Enterprise Relational System for a fine art interiors designs company to automate and control the information flow through all designs, productions, sales and financial management. A web based application developed using Ext JS + CSS for Client Side and PHP + Symfony + Postgres SQL for Server Side
- Develop of specific tools to optimize the use of materials in a production process
- Develop and maintain reports from legacy systems

09/2014 to 09/2016

PHP Web Developer

WebCubana – Cuba, La Havana

· Created web applications and components using PHP programming language

09/2014 to 09/2016

System Administrator

Habaguanex S.A – Cuba, La Havana

- Introduced Windows Serversinfrastructure and management tools to create and manage virtual server computing environment
- Identified and eliminated website bugs to improve user experience
- Established network specifications and analyzed workflow, access, information and security requirements

SKILLS

- PHP, Symfony and CodeIgniter Framework
- C#, .Net Framework MVC
- Net Core RESTful Api
- HTML5 + CSS 3+ JavaScripts, JQuery, Ext Js, Boostrap
- Database design, MySQL, Postgres Sql, MSSQL
- Full-cycle software development
- ERP System implementation

EDUCATION

07/2014

Engineer's Degree, Computer Software Engineering

Universidad de las Ciencias Informáticas (UCI) - La Habana, Cuba 5-year degree in computer science focused on the complete cycle of application development (web based & desktop based), develop methodologies, design patterns, systems engineering, networking.